<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Relax Home</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="Register">Register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string-array name="CLEANING">
        <item>HOME CLEANZ CLEANING and LAUNDRY SERVICES</item>
        <item>HOUSE CLEANER SINGAPORESINGAPORE</item>
        <item>NTUC DOMESTIC CLEANING SERVICE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="CleaningDetail">
        <item>Home Cleanz is founded in 2004 by 2 young graduates from the School of Design and Environment, National University of Singapore.
            We started out with a simple aim, which is to provide home cleaning services to busy professionals.
            Differentiating ourselves from the competition in the industry, we place particularly strong emphasis on our company’s service quality and after-sales service.
            We never stop learning to improve ourselves to serve our clients well. And because
            of this attitude throughout the company, we build strong and harmonious relationships with many customers.
            This is our thirteen year into our business, and we have not looked back since.
            We will continue to push ourselves to a greater height and always constantly innovate to excel in our business!</item>
        <item>Singapore is one of the few countries on the planet, Earth where its residents enjoy the pride of living an elegant life.
            Indeed, hundreds and thousands of homeowners achieve the beauty and elegance of their houses/homes/offices by employing different methods;
            which include keeping pets, flooring the house with beautiful tiles (and other kinds of flooring materials such as engineered wood flooring,
            laminate flooring, marble flooring, and so on), while others make their rooms nicer by covering the floors with amazingly good carpets, and many more.
            Nevertheless, this article dwells on carpets as well as ways of retaining its beauty. </item>
        <item>Enjoy convenient domestic assistance to supplement your busy lifestyle. All domestic cleaners [1] are trained before being assigned job requests.

Two types of packages are available to meet the varying needs of households.
            Weekly Cleaning is for general regular house cleaning on a regular basis and One-Time Cleaning is suitable for new homes or spring cleaning before a festive season.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="CleaningWebsite">
        <item>www.homecleanz.com</item>
        <item>www.housecleanersingapore.com </item>
        <item>Nwww.income.com.sg/domestic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="CleaningAddress">
        <item>wsalesenquiry@homecleanz.com</item>
        <item>- </item>
        <item>Nwww.income.com.sg/domestic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="PLUMBER">
        <item>SGPLUMBING</item>
        <item>MR. PLUMBER SINGAPORE</item>
        <item>HDB PLIMBERS</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ELECTRICIAN">
        <item>ELECTRICIAN SINGAPORE</item>
        <item>DAYLIGHT ELECTRICIAN </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
